Sir it is within 6% to 10%
Sir excuse
me hold it hold it Sir please wait a
little Sir one sat a sat at
a time
Look at the center Sir
look at the center for a
minute or two Good afternoon Ya good to go Okay Okay Hi Good
afternoon Every one My name is Vivek
Srivastava I am from ICS Lobad
and I am part of health team in
ICSC Ulambard Very warm welcome to each one
of you and I think we have launched a
new product which is
elevated that if you have any questions anything which we have already present brief about the
product If you have any doubt any question
feel free to please
ask Okay So let me just  Briefly tell you about the
product this is a first of its kind product which
we have
launched for health
customers in india this product is
designed which has a unique features
which are there which primarily takes
care of the basic need of any customer
this product is designed keeping one
phenomena in feature in mind that there
are various type of customers in the
market and everyone requires a product
which is suits him and has to be very
very unique or or personalized in  nature
we have designed this product which is
purely customizable you can design
customize as per your need and it is
backed by artificial intelligence also
more importantly it has got many unique
features which are industry first which
is there not there in the industry
as a whole we have introduced our new
add on cover which is there in this
product which is infinite care it tells
it says that in the life time of the
policy one claim of unlimited amount can
be taken by any customer which is not
there unheard of in the industry itself
not only this many other features  like
cumulative bonus which is also an add on
cover  which can be bought as per the
need of the customer which says that
every year 100% bonus will be given to
the customer and this can go up to
unlimited times currently in the market
there are add on benefits like
cumulative bonus which goes up to a
certain times in the life time of the
policy but in our policy we have said it
can go up to unlimited time we have
reset benefit which is already there
also we have introduced a unique feature
which is a jump start this gives a
flexibility to cover any pre existing
customer of which  is there with any
customer and it will give a unique
feature which says that you need not to
wait for three years to start coverage
of those pds which are there which is
pre existing disease you
have the
the pd will get covered from 31st day so
that is again a unique proposition for
our customers and again i am saying that
it is very much customizable you can
personalize as per your requirement no
need of buying or mandatory covers are
there it is completely to the
flexibility of the customers we have
just launched this  product and the
response which we are getting on this
product  is really amazing so thank you
all for making this product launch
very very successful thank you
so my name is Amita Anand and I
will represent ICICI Bank basically what
we met today everything we
talked about earlier was about the Elevate product
we so this is the
first time what is the Elevate product okay
something first time we mean
this is the first product in the insurance industry with such features no
one has launched till now those features which we talked about earlier we talked about
infinite sum insured so
we have launched a feature which no one has launched till now in the insurance industry here
instead of sum insured of 10 lakhs 20 lakhs 30 lakhs crore rupees
we are offering infinite sum insured in the
same way the customer should pay less premium should his sum
insured increase every year
customer should pay less premium my sum insured should increase every year  If we take the
add-on feature called Power Booster,
every year, whatever sum
insured is doubled. The
third feature comes and wherever the customer has pre-
existing diseases like diabetes,
hypertension, asthma,
etc., all these things can be covered
from the first day without any waiting period. A
customer who wants to get coverage from the first day can get coverage by
taking the feature called Gem Start and get it on Day One.
Similarly, we have
customers who want cashless treatment not only in non-network
hospitals but also in non-network
hospitals. We
provide our customers with the value-added feature called Cashless Anywhere. That is also a
unique feature. If you look at the market today, if you look at the company that
uses this feature and
provides this facility, ICICI Bank,
after we launched it,
it also came in the IRDA regulation. Now,
IRDA is also saying that even if a customer
goes to any hospital, they can get cashless treatment.
Whatever
resolution comes out or whatever IRDA
norm comes out, we implement it a year in advance.
Similarly, if
we see a product in the market, generally, we
give it as a package, adding five or six
benefits, all the covers, and if
you want health insurance, you can't say
forcefully,
but they make it as a package. In the
same way,
what we are doing in our Elevate product is that we are
giving 22 different add-ons. Whoever wants it,
whoever wants a feature according to their requirement,
he opts for that feature, and
accordingly, he pays the premium and
whatever coverage the policy has, he
gets it for life. Apart from this, if we are in
jobs, there is medical everywhere. There is
an age bracket after which there is medical in
every company. So in our
product, in the Elevate product, we have
Medicals are not a trigger somewhere,
according to the sum insured, but otherwise,
according to age, but not a trigger. Any particular thing
is more than the average, that is, only there, depending upon the
underwriting
guidelines. We trigger medicals,
but as a generic, where it is not a trigger.
We do not have an age limit. Most likely,
many people are asking,
till what age do we cover? There is no
age limit in this product.
We give the customer a policy regardless of how old they are. We give the customer a fitment
according to our underwriting rules and norms, that is,
not 100 years old, but
even an individual who is 120 years old can give a health insurance policy.
What is the best product in Elevate?
Sir, the response is great.
We launched Elevate on July 1st. There is a
tremendous response. We
say that if we see it in movies, we will call it a super duper
hit. This product is also
in the market, that is, general.  Health
insurance is called a little push
product, that is, it can only be
promoted well and hard,
right? But when you look at this particular
product, there are so many features that we are
talking about everywhere, infinite, infinite, infinite. Because of what we have
done,
this has become a pull product in India, that is, the
customer or the channel is asking,
what is this product, my customer is saying, this product is
needed, so there
is such a pull. Sir, if we look at the claim ratio, it has been
only a month since the product was launched,
so I cannot talk about claims on this particular product,
but if we look at it generically, the
market knows more than I can say. ICI
Lombard says that claims will be settled like butter, so the
market knows,
I don't need to say, sir,
how much support has this policy received, sir, if there are
no pre-existing diseases, that is,
two  The policy will be issued in three minutes.
Okay, if there is a pre-
existing disease, we will
issue the policy within 24 hours. You can do it online.
Waiting period. What are the waiting periods? If you
have taken a jump start for pre-existing diseases,
I will give you coverage for 31 days. If you do
not take a jump start, there will be a
waiting period of three years.